{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "4x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 16. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 4.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(16x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 81. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 9.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 49. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 7.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3√(3)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 12. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 3, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(12x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(3x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 3. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(3x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 36. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 6.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 64. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 8.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 49. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 7.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(2x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(3x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 12. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 3, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(12x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(6)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 6. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(7)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 64. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 8.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(2x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 18. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 3, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(18x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "First look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 2. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(2x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 2. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(2x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 81. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 9.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 100. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 10.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^2", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 49. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 7.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(7x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(3)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 3. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(3x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 64. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 8.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(3x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 3. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(3x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^2", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 36. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 6.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(5x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 20. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 5, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(20x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(15x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 15. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(15x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 100. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 10.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(7)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 100. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 10.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(10)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 10. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(3)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 12. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 3, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(12x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(6)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 6. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(2x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 64. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 8.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(5)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 5. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 16. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 4.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(16x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(5x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 5. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 16. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 4.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(16x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3", "explanation": "First look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 25. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 5.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(25x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 100. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 10.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(3x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 3. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(3x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(7)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 36. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 6.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(7)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(7)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 100. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 10.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(30)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 30. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(30x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(3)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 3. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(3x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(7x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 2. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(2x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(10x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 10. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(10x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(7x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x√(2)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 8. \nSince the number is a multiple of a perfect square, we pull out the perfect square number\u0027s root, 2, and leave the remaining factor, 2, inside.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 49. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 7.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 81. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 9.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 100. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 10.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 81. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 9.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 49. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 7.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 3.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 1 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 36. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 6.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(6x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 6. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 16. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 4.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(16x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(5)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 5. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 4.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5x^4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 4. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 2.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(4x)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x√(5)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 5. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 2.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(5x^2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^2√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 49. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 7.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(49x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2√(6x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 6. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 5.\nSince the exponent is odd, we pull out the variable by subtracting 1 from the variable exponent and dividing it by 2. That makes 2 the exponent for the variable outside the square root and 1 the exponent for the variable inside the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(6x^5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^3√(7)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 7. \nSince the number is not a perfect square, or a multiple of a perfect square, we will just leave it inside the square root.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 6.\nSince the exponent is even, we can just pull out the whole variable and divide the exponent by 2.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(7x^6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(x)", "explanation": "First look at the coefficient: 9. \nSince the number is a perfect square, we can pull out the root of the number, 3.\n\nThen look at the variable\u0027s exponent: 1.\nSince the exponent is 1, we leave the variable under the square root.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(9x)", "type": "text"}
]}